<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Whisker's Blog - Learn all about blockchain, cryptography and more!]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Whisker's Blog - Learn all about blockchain, cryptography and more!]]></description>
        <link>https://whisker17.vercel.app/</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 08:13:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://whisker17.vercel.app/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Meta Transactions (Written by Notion AI)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Meta transactions enable users to interact with blockchain applications without directly paying gas fees by utilizing relayers, making blockchain more accessible while discussing their benefits in gaming, finance, and identity management, along with their current limitations.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/metatx-ai</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/metatx-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERC-4337 - From Zero To Hero]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ERC-4337 introduces Account Abstraction through a system of smart contract wallets, bundlers, paymasters, and aggregators, evolving from basic EOA+CA model to a comprehensive solution that enables more flexible transaction handling and better user experience on Ethereum.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/erc-4337</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/erc-4337</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Deep Dive into Cannon]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog explores how Cannons work in the op stack, which is a fraud proof system designed by Optimism.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/cannon-deep-dive</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/cannon-deep-dive</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 13:28:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Batch calls in Substrate]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article explains how Substrate's batch calls functionality allows users to execute multiple transactions with a single signature through the utility.batch method, improving user experience by reducing the number of required signatures while maintaining security.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/batch-calls-in-substrate</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/batch-calls-in-substrate</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Strong Account in Substrate - Proxy Account]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article provides a comprehensive overview of Substrate's Proxy Account functionality, explaining how account security can be enhanced by splitting account functionalities into different proxy accounts with varying permissions]]></description>
            <link>/posts/proxy-pallet</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/proxy-pallet</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Deep Dive into Kroma's ZK Fraud Proof Design]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog explores how Kroma implement a zk fraud proof system.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/kroma</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/kroma</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MultiSig in Substrate]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog explores how MultiSig works in Substrate.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/multisig-in-substrate</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/multisig-in-substrate</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fraud Proof in OP Stack]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog explores how fraud proofs work in the op stack.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/fraud-proof-in-op-stack</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/fraud-proof-in-op-stack</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 13:28:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Deep Dive into RIP-7560]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog explores how RIP-7560 works, which is a native Account Abstraction proposal in Ethereum ecosystem.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/rip-7560</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/rip-7560</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Provide Shared Security for Multiple Chains]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article compares different approaches to providing shared security across multiple chains, focusing on how Polkadot's parachain design and Cosmos' Interchain Security tackle this challenge, while also briefly discussing Ethereum's Rollup solutions for context.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/shared-security</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/shared-security</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to make our wallets more user-friendly]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article explains Substrate's Session Keys functionality, which improves wallet user experience and security by allowing users to set temporary hot keys for specific operations, eliminating the need for frequent password input.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/session-keys</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/session-keys</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shamir Secret Share Intros]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article explains Shamir Secret Sharing (SSS), a cryptographic protocol that uses polynomial interpolation to split a secret into multiple shares, requiring a predetermined number of shares to reconstruct the original secret, making it useful for secure key management and access control systems.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/shamir-secret-sharing</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/shamir-secret-sharing</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social Recovery in Substrate]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article explains Substrate's Social Recovery functionality, which allows users to regain access to their lost accounts through a system of pre-designated trusted friends who must reach a threshold consensus, enhancing wallet security and user experience while maintaining safeguards against malicious recovery attempts.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/social-recovery</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/social-recovery</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How a Robust Account System Should Be Designed]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The article presents Substrate's account system as a well-thought-out solution that addresses many of the limitations present in other blockchain account systems, particularly compared to Ethereum's ERC-4337.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/substrate-account</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/substrate-account</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Develop ZK Fraud Proof with RISC0]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This blog explores how to use Risc0 to build a zk fraud proof system.]]></description>
            <link>/posts/zk-fraud-proof-by-using-risc0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/zk-fraud-proof-by-using-risc0</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:28:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>